DENZEL MAXINO

0917 112 6687 | maxino.denzel@gmail.com | Malate, Manila | https://www.linkedin.com/in/denmax

SUMMARY

I am a **Registered Mechanical Engineer** with 2+ years of work experience. I have a range of knowledge in mechanical, electrical, fire protection, gas, and plumbing facilities and reviewing of plans in accordance to the established standards

EDUCATION

B.S. Mechanical Engineering

Mapúa Institute of Technology

2011 - 2016

HIGHLIGHTS

- AutoCAD
- Microsoft Office & OpenOffice
- BOSH Training (40 hours)
- PLC & SCADA Training

- TOEIC Professional Proficiency (2015)
- 10th Board Topnotcher (2017)

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2018 - Present

Puregold Realty Leasing & Management, Inc.

Property Management Unit - Mechanical Engineer

- Inspected and identified new and existing problems of electro-mechanical, fire protection, and plumbing facilities of property companies including evaluation of maintenance and service reports, overseeing and documentation of preventive maintenance and repair history
- Produced scope of works, coordinated with contractors, and evaluated submitted quotations
- Contributed in establishing the company's standard design guidelines and inspection checklist for tenant spaces, with regards to mechanical, fire protection, gas and electrical
- Reviewed tenant submitted blueprints relating to mechanical and gas
- Inspected tenant construction and mall construction in coordination with the architect and other engineering disciplines

May 2017 – Apr 2018

Middleby Worldwide Philippines

Management Trainee (May 2017 – Nov 2017); Sales Engineer (Nov 2017 – Apr 2018)

- Managed accounts and maintained the relationship between client and company
- Measured and inspected site during and after construction or renovation
- Produced and consulted on client's kitchen layouts when requested
- Coordinated with engineering department with the design of fabricated equipment in accordance to the request of the client, issues projected and found, and quality of life improvements